Chasani Douglas

Driven professional Fullstack Engineer focusing in Angular and Ruby on Rails with 7 years of experience of web development experience. Developed in agile environments where teamwork and communication were imperative in accomplishing deadlines.

624 Cambridge St.
Allston, MA 02134
(845) 820-1750
chasanid@gmail.com
www.cjdouglas.com
www.linkedin.com/in/chasani

EXPERIENCE

Gamer Sensei, Boston, MA— Full Stack Developer

March 2016 - Present

Helped Gamer Sensei grow over 15 times by having a strong hand in the speccing and developing of major site improvements such as Gamer Sensei's complete redesign, virtual currency system, and user dashboard portals. Refined recurring workflows including the Git flow, production deployments to Heroku, and interviewing/onboarding new hires.

ESPN, Inc., Bristol, CT— Web Developer I

June 2012 - October 2015

Front End Developer creating APIs for in-house and third party applications, such as espn.com and the ESPN app. In charge of emergency maintence of the APIs once a week every month. Quickly became proficient in Groovy, Bootstrap, AngularJs and a proprietary language named Tea as demanded for the job.

University of Hartford, West Hartford, CT— Web Developer

April 2011 - May 2013

Develop, design, and maintain the following websites for the Admissions Department at the University of Hartford: Winter-term, Summer-term, and Paralegal. In charge of training the next hire.

University of Hartford, West Hartford, CT— *Tutor*

August 2010 - May 2013

In charge of monitoring the computer lab while assisting students with their school work.

EDUCATION

University of Hartford, West Hartford, CT— B.A.

August 2009 - May 20-13

Multimedia Web Design and Development with a specialization in Human Computer Interaction – Division I Athlete

Front End Technologies

Javascript

AngularJs

JQuery

Ajax JSON

HTML 5

Responsive CSS3

Bourbon/Neat

SCSS

Bootstrap

Backend Technologies

Ruby on Rails 4/5

Git/GitHub

OOP

SOL

Postgres

MySQL

RESTful APIs

Development/Docs

AWARDS

Junior Achievement Award in

Web Development-

University of Hartford

Dean's List (4 Years)-

University of Hartford

UH Presidential Scholarship-

University of Hartford